[{"answer": " Hello, my friend, trouble", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " my friend. Yes, tonight's his crucial night. You're right, we'll have to send someone down immediately. Whose turn is it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Oh  my friend. Hasn't got his wings yet, has he? We've passed him up right along", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Yes, but he's got the faith of a child  simple. my friend, send for my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " No, worse. He's discouraged. At exactly te", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " You will spend that hour getting acquainted with my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Oh, thank you, sir. Thank you", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Sit down? What are..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Now you're talkin'. Gee whiz, I could use this as a raft in case the boat sunk. How much does this cost", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "That's my trick ear, my friend. It sounded as if you said no charge", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hi, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sorry, Pop. I didn't mean that remark, but this business of nickels and dimes and spending all your life trying to figure out how to save three cents on a length of pipe... I'd go crazy. I want to do something big and something important", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I know, Dad. I wish I felt... But I've been hoarding pennies like a miser in order to... Most of my friends have already finished college. I just feel like if I don't get away, I'd bust", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I guess I'm not quite the football type.  You... look wonderful. You know, if it wasn't me talking I'd say you were the prettiest girl in town", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't know. Maybe I will say it. How old are you anyway", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, no", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "If I told you it might not come true", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Yeah, I'll be right down", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I wonder what's going on in there", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hmmm", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well, she's not crazy about him", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes. my friend's crazy about my friend", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, how do you know? Did she discuss it with you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Who's down there with you", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " my friend? What's he want", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh, well, that's awfully sweet of you, my friend.  There's an old friend of yours here. my friend", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes, old mos", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Wait a minute. I'll call him.  my friend", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "He does so. He asked for him.  Geo... my friend, my friend wants to speak to you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "A toast! A toast to Papa Dollar and to Mama Dollar, and if you want the old Building and Loan to stay in business, you better have a family real quick", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I wish they were too. Okay, let's put them in the safe and see what happens", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hey, this is the company's posters, and the company won't like this", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Sure I have, but I got rid of it", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, they are, are they? Even though they know the Baileys haven't made a dime out of it", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Well, you are not me", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Fort", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "My point? My point is, I want to hire you", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "All right, sir", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Okay, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " ...now tell me about it", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What man", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "my friend  bank examiner", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Merry Christmas", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "We're all excited around here.  My brother just got the Congressional Medal of Honor. The President just decorated him", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Good year? Well, between you and me, Mr. my friend, we're broke", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Wrong? Everything's wrong! You call this a happy family? Why did we have to have all these kids", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " I don't know. Ask your mother", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Wait now. Where do you think you're going", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "All right, all right. Here, give Daddy the flower. I'll give it a drink", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You what? To save me", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Go through with what", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "It's against the law to commit suicide around here", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Where do you come from", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "What'd you say", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Oh, you mustn't say things like that. You...  ...wait a minute. Wait a minute. That's an idea.  What do you think? Yeah, that'll do it.  All right.  You've got your wish. You've never been born", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sorry. I'll stroll. You fly", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You haven't got your wings. Yeah, that's right", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well then, why am I seeing all these strange things", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Then if I wasn't born, who am I", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Hey... hey. Where did the Building and Loan move to", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "The Bailey Building and Loan. It was up there", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Hey, Violet!  Hey, listen  that's my friend", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "I know that girl", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Look here, my friend, straighten me out here.  I've got some bad liquor or something.  Listen to me now. Now, you are my friend Bishop, and you live in that place with your wife and kid? That's right, isn't it", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " Seen your wife? I've been to your house a hundred times", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Get over what? I don't take in strangers unless they're sent here by somebody I know", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": " You know him", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": " I've heard of things like this. You've got me in some kind of a spell, or something.  Well, I'm going to get out of it. I'll get out of it. I know how, too. I... the last man I talked to before all this stuff started happening to me was my friend", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Sure I know where he lives. He lives in that place", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Where's my friend", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend, my friend", "docId": "wonderfullife.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "You have no idea what happened..", "qsentId": 74}]